Hello, and welcome to the demonstration.
This subtitle file is intentionally complex.
Line one of a multi-line cue.
Line two continues the thought.
Line three finishes it.
Hi.
At 3:45 PM on 12/31/2025, agent 007 entered room 404.
He said, "We need exactly 100% accuracy!"
It's a test of apostrophes and "nested quotes".
Em dash test — hyphen-minus - and ellipsis...
ALL CAPS SHOULD REMAIN STABLE IN SOURCE.
Speaker A: Are you ready?
Speaker B: Always.
[Music playing softly]
- First bullet point
- Second bullet point
URL reference: https://example.com/path?q=1
Email-style text: user@example.org
Tab-separated	words	and   multiple   spaces.
Unicode symbols: café, naïve, 日本語, emoji test.
¿Hablas español? ¡Por supuesto!
Mathematical tokens: x^2 + y^2 = z^2, and 3.14159.
Path-like text: C:\Users\Demo\file.srt
HTML entities: &amp; &lt;tag&gt;
Repeated word word word for alignment checks.
Question? Exclamation! Statement.
A much longer cue that spans a wider window so timing boundaries stay independent while the translation mapping remains one cue to one translated block without proportional splitting errors.
Short again.
Penultimate cue with comma, semicolon; colon: end.
Final cue — thanks for watching.
♪ Closing theme ♪
The end.